Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, Commissions and Committees, 1947-1971; 8
  - Miscellaneous Conferences, Commissions and Committees, 1945-1963; 8.5; 2 cubic ft.
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Teachers' Salaries Publications (Binder), [1951?] (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - Commission on Municipal Revenues and Reduction of Real Estate Taxes - Memoranda, 1945; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15-16)
    - New York State Temporary Commission on School Buildings - Commission on School Buildings (Binder 1 of 2), 1950 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17)
    - New York State Temporary Commission on School Buildings - Commission on School Buildings (Binder 2 of 2), 1950; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 18-19)
    - New York State Temporary Commission on School Buildings - Commission on School Buildings (Binder 1 of 2), 1952-1953; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20-21)
    - New York State Temporary Commission on School Buildings - Commission on School Buildings (Binder 2 of 2), 1952-1953; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22-23)
    - New York State Temporary Commission on School Buildings - Information Bulletins, 1951 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 24)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems (Binder), 1956 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 25)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems -Proceedings of the National Conference on Metropolitan Problems, 1956 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 26)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems -Proceedings of the National Conference on Metropolitan Problems, 1956 (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems - Reports Adopted by National Conference on Metropolitan Problems, 1956 (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems - Continuing National Conference on Metropolitan Problems (Binder), 1957; 2 folders (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3-4)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Problems - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Board of Directors Meeting, 1/24/1958 (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5)
    - Committee on Special Local Non-Property Taxes - Local Non-Property Tax Committee, 1949; 3 binders (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 6-8)
    - Committee on Special Local Non-Property Taxes - Local Non-Property Tax Committee, 1949-1950; 3 folders (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9-11)
    - Committee on Special Local Non-Property Taxes - Local Non-Property Tax Committee (Binder), 1951; 2 folders (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12-13)
    - Committee on Special Local Non-Property Taxes - Local Non-Property Tax Committee (Binder), 1952 (Box 40 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
- Publications, 1932-1976; 9; 3.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains publications accumulated by Moore, including periodicals and printed reports. It includes both publications by external sources and the publications of organizations with which Moore served, such as the Government Affairs Foundation and the New York State Commission on School Buildings. The series is organized alphabetically by the name of the author or issuing organization and by title when that information is not given. It includes an extensive file of New York State publications from various government divisions, mostly related to state and municipal finance, as well as numerous publications from third-party groups, such as the Institute of Assessing Officers and the American Institute of Real Estate Appraisers. It also includes copies of Governor Rockefeller's messages to the legislature.
  - Academic Heraldry Leaflet, 1951 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Academy for Educational Development The Legislature and Higher Education in New York State, 1964 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations New Proposals for 1969: ACIR State Legislative Program, 1968 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, Pamphlet, 1967 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Report for 1965 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Report for 1966 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Report for 1967 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Allen, James E. Jr.The Court and Public Education with Particular Reference to New York State, 1966 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - American Association for State and Local History History News (Periodical), 1965-1966 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 23)
  - American Institute of Real Estate Appraisers Schedule of 1969 Case Study Courses (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 24)
  - American Society of Public Administration Capital District Chapter Annual Report, 1968 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Assessors' Information Digest, 1968-1969 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Assessors' News Letter, 1968-1969 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Assessors' Topics, 1969-1970 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Axel, Robert.Trends and Relationships in Public Assistance in the United States, 1940-1952: A Statistical Analysis (Government Affairs Foundation Report), 1954 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Belkin, Samuel Profile of Courage, 1963 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Binghamton Commission on Architecture and Urban Design The First Three Years: 1964-1967, 1968 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Brookings Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Brounshidle Post Legionnaire, Vol. 11 No. 5, 1970 February (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Campbell, Alan K., and Jesse Burkhead Public Policy for Urban America, 1968 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Carnegie Quarterly, Vol. 17 No. 2, 1969 Spring (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Ceremonies at the Rededication of Court of Appeals Hall, 1959 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 36)
  - City of Brantford, Ontario.Financial Statement and Auditors' Report, 1968 (Box 40 (9-Publications), Folder 37)
  - Commission on Governmental Revision of Nassau County A New Charter for Nassau County: Proposed Report to the Board of Supervisors, 1966 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Committee on Governmental Operations Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations: The First Five Years, 1966 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Committee for Economic Development A Stabilizing Fiscal and Monetary Policy for 1970, 1969 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Committee for Economic Development Financing a Better Election System, 1968 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Committee for Economic Development Improving Executive Management in the Federal Government, 1964 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Committee for Economic Development Improving the Public Welfare System, 1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Committee for Economic Development Reshaping Government in Metropolitan Areas, 1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Computer Environments Corporation Seminar Programs, 1969 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Development and Problems of Grants in Aid in the Tax System of New York State (Master's Thesis, Alice Wood Wynd), 1952 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 9-10)
  - Donoghue, James R.The Local Government System of Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Fire District Affairs, Vol. 4 No. 6, 1976 November (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Georgia Government Review, Vol. 2 No. 1, 1969 Winter (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Gould, Samuel B.The First Rung of the Ladder, 1964 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Government Affairs Foundation Appendix: Federal Block Grants to States for Public Welfare Purposes, 1954 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Government Affairs Foundation Bibliography: Local Government in New York State During the Dutch Period, 1968 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Government Affairs Foundation State Constitutional Restrictions on Local Borrowing and Property Taxing Powers, 1965 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - IAO Journal (Institute of Assessing Officers), 1969 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Research, Vol. 11 No. 1, 1965 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - International Association of Assessing Officers Newsletter, Vol. 36 No. 1, 1970 January (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - International Conference on Assessment Administration, Program, 1969 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Johnstown in New York State's Mohawk Valley, 1941 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Local Non-Property Tax Committee - First Report, 1950 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Local Non-Property Tax Committee - Second Report, 1951 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Lutz, Edward A.Some Problems and Alternatives in Developing Federal Block Grants to States for Public Welfare Purposes (Government Affairs Foundation Report), 1954 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Man and Manager, Inc.Employee Discipline: A Special Report, Undated (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Area Digest, 1969 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Area Digest (Newsletter of the SUNY Graduate School of Public Affairs), 1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Surveys, 1961-1963 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters and Press Releases, 1956-1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Municipal Affairs Review, 1969-1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Municipal News, Vol. 59, No. 24, 1969 May (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Municipal Police Training Council Our First Six Months: A Progress Report, 1959 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Municipal Police Training Council Municipal Police Training in New York State, Undated (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 34)
  - National Association of County Officials The Urban County Congress of the National Association of County Officials, Undated (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 35)
  - National Service to Regional Councils Newsletter, No. 31, 1969 October (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 36)
  - National Service to Regional Councils Regional Council Profiles, 1969 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 37)
  - National Service to Regional Councils Regional Review Quarterly (Newsletter), 1969-1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 38)
  - New Jersey Department of Community Affairs Annual Report, 1968 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 39)
  - New York City Housing Authority New Neighborhoods, New Lives, 1964 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 40)
  - New York City Temporary Commission on City Finances Better Financing for New York City, 1966 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 41)
  - New York City Temporary Commission on City Finances Blueprint For Fiscal Improvement, 1966 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 42)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce New York City Finances: A Ten Year Review, 1964 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 43)
  - New York Library Association NYLA Bulletin (Periodical), Vol. 12 No. 4, 1964 July-1964 August (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 44)
  - New York Republican State Committee New York Report, 1965 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 45)
  - New York State Advisory Committee on Teacher's Salaries Report on Teacher's Salaries, 1951 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 46)
  - New York State Assembly Ways and Means Committee The New York State Budget and You, 1965 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 47)
  - New York State Assessors' Association Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 48)
  - New York State Bar Association Municipal Law Section: Fall Meeting (Program), 1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 49)
  - New York State Board of Social Welfare.A Century of Dedication, 1967 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 50)
  - New York State Budget Summary, 1965-1966 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 51)
  - New York State Civil Defense Commission Annual Report, 1970 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 52)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws.Memorandum Number Two: State Support for Public Schools in New York as Related to Tax Relief and Educational Expansion, 1937 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 53)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws.Memorandum Number Four: Turnover of Title to Real Property in New York, Undated (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 54)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws.Memorandum Number Six: Sales Taxes on Selected Commodities, 1932 (Box 41 (9-Publications), Folder 55)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws Memorandum Number Seven: Retail and General Sales Taxes, 1932 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws Memorandum Number Eight: The Revenue Problem of Tax-Limit Cities, 1932 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws Memorandum Number Eleven: Use of Reserve Funds to Stabilize Revenue Available for Expenditure, 1932 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws Memorandum Number Twelve: The Collection of Real Estate Taxes in New York, 1932 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - New York State Commission on Governmental Operations of the City of New York Background Research on the Top Structure of the Government of the City of New York, 1961 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - New York State Commission on Municipal Revenues and Reduction of Real Estate Taxes Report to Governor, 1944; typescript (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - New York State Commission on Municipal Revenues and Reduction of Real Estate Taxes, Report, 1945; 2 folders (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 7-8)
  - New York State Commission on Municipal Revenues and Reduction of Real Estate Taxes, Report, 1946 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings A Picture of Progress, 1954 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings Doorway to Better Schools (Fourth Report), 1953 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings Economies from A to Z in Planning and Building Schools, 1953 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings More Schools for Your Money!, 1954 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings The School Building Problem in the City of New York (First Report), 1951 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings Toward Better Schools (Second Report), 1951 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - New York State Commission on School Buildings Toward Better Schools (Third Report), 1952 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - New York State Countil on the Arts Annual Report, 1962 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, Untitled Report, 1960-1964 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Annual Report, 1966 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control 1967 Annual Report of the Comptroller (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control A Preview of Local Government, 1945-1955; 1945 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control Financial Data for School Districts, Year Ending June 30, 1965, 1966 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control History of the Comptroller's Office: A Condensation, 1967 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 23)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control Index to the Public Schools and Mail Directory of Local Governments, 1965 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 24)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control New York State's Comptrollers: 50 Guardians of the Public Purse, 1965 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 25)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control State Aid to Local Government, 1966 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 26)
  - New York State Department of Audit and Control State Aid to Local Government, 1967 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 27)
  - New York State Department of Commerce New York State Business Fact Book: 1968 Supplement (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 28)
  - New York State Department of Commerce Quarterly Summary of Business Statistics, 1967 January-1967 March (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 29)
  - New York State Division of the Budget Budget Summary, 1957-1958 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 30)
  - New York State Division of the Budget Budget Summary, 1966-1967 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 31)
  - New York State Division of the Budget New York State Index of Federal and State Assistance Programs, 1968 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 32)
  - New York State Education Department Analysis of School Finances: New York State School Districts 1967-1968, 1969 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 33)
  - New York State Education Department Federal Aid Paid to New York School Districts 1966-1967: An Analysis, 1969 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 34)
  - New York State Education Department The Regional Support of Education in the Albany Capital Area, 1968 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 35)
  - New York State Education Department Studies of Public School Support 1968 Series, 1969 (Box 42 (9-Publications), Folder 36)
  - New York State Office of Planning Coordination Demographic Projections for New York State Counties (Preliminary Extracts), 1968 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - New York State Personnel News, Vol. 23, No. 3, 1969 May (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - New York State Temporary State Commission on Per Capita Aid,First Report, 1963; 2 folders (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 3-4)
  - New York State Temporary State Commission on Per Capita Aid,Second Report, 1964 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Office for Local Government Newsletter, 1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Olson Electronics, Catalog, [1970?] (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Opinion (Buffalo Law School Newspaper), 1970-1971 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Phillips, Walter M.A Future for Penjerdel, 1965 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Political Science at Chapel Hill, 1966-1967 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Proposed Reorganization of the Executive Branch of New York State Government: Report to Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller And Governor's Memorandum to the Legislature, 1959 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Public Administration News, 1969-1970 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Public Administration News: Management Forum, 1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Public Administration Recruiter, 1969-1970 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Public Administration Review, 1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Public Administration Review, 1970 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Public Affairs Comment, Vol. 15, No. 1, 1969 January (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Publishers' Catalogs, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Quarterly Summary of State and Local Tax Revenue, 1968-1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Regional Plan Associaton The Future of Nassau County, 1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Regional Plan News No. 91, 1969 September (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.The Executive Budget: The Governor's Message Including Appendices, 1961-1962 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Governor's Message to the Legislature, 1962 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Governor's Message to the Legislature, 1963 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Governor's Message to the Legislature, 1964 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Governor's Message to the Legislature, 1965 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Message to the Legislature and Inaugural Address, 1967 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Governor's Message to the Legislature, 1968 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Governor's Message to the Legislature, 1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Second Inaugural Address, 1963 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Siren, 1969-1970 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 31)
  - State Board of Equalization and Assessment Principles and Procedures Used in Establishing State Equalization Rates, 1961 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 32)
  - State Board of Equalization and Assessment Property Tax Assessment in the United States: Preliminary Report, 1961 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 33)
  - State Tax Review Vol. 30, No. 17, 1969 April 29 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 34)
  - State University of New York at Albany Graduate School of Public Affairs Local Government In-Service Training: An Annotated Bibliography (Sponsored by Government Affairs Foundation, 1968 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 35)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo, Midyear Commencement Program, 1965 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 36)
  - SUNY - Albany Graduate School of Public Affairs Local Government In - Service Training: An Annotated Bibliography (Sponsored by Government Affairs Foundation), 1968 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 37)
  - SUNY - Albany Graduate School of Public Affairs 1968 Metropolitan Surveys (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 38)
  - Tax Foundation Library Bulletin, 1969 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Thirteen Thirteen Center for Public Administration Vol. 4, No. 5, 1969 May-1969 June (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Tri-State Transportation Commission Regional Forecast 1985: The Future Size and Needs of the Tri-State Region, 1967 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 41)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee A Consultant's Report to the Tri - State Transportation Committee on a Reconnaissance of the Tri-State Region, 1965 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 42)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights Equal Opportunity in Farm Programs: An Appraisal of Services Rendered by Agencies of the United States Department of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 43)
  - United States Congress Joint Economic Committee, Subcommittee on Urban Affairs Urban America: Goals and Problems, 1967 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 44)
  - United States Department of Commerce Bureau of the Census Criminal Justice: Expenditure and Employment for Selected Large Governmental Units, 1966-1967 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 45)
  - United States Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census Public Employment in 1968 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 46)
  - University of Buffalo Alumni News, 1969 June (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 47)
  - Williams, Lawrence K.Two Articles on Automation, 1964 (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 48)
  - World Peace Through Law Center Bulletin, Vol. 6 No. 4, 1959 April (Box 43 (9-Publications), Folder 49)
- Speeches, 1934-1969; 10; 10 cubic ft.